Welcome to the ENHANCE alliance
Bienvenido a, la alianza ENHANCE
Welcome to the ENHANCE alliance
Bienvenido a la alianza ENHANCE
[hesitation]
[vacilación]
this is an alliance of seven leading European universities
esta es una alianza de siete principales universidades europeas
with a focus on science and engineering
con un enfoque en la ciencia y la ingeniería
improving partnerships working under the umbrella of the european
el mejorar alianzas trabajando bajo el paraguas de la european
university towards another more integrated European initiative
university hacia otra iniciativa europeo más integrado
university a student network and staff mobility
university a red estudiante y la movilidad del personal
innovative ways of learning and closing the engagement with society
formas innovadoras de aprendizaje y cerrar el compromiso con la sociedad
at all levels
en todos los niveles
women's hands is to create a new new European academic space
las mujeres manos es crear un nuevo espacio académico europeo
for interaction between innovating technological progress
para la interacción entre innovando progreso tecnológico
society and the natural environment committed to social elias
la sociedad y el entorno natural se ha comprometido a elías social
inclusion run science and research and research and sustainable education
inclusión ejecutar la ciencia y la investigación y la educación sostenible
technology want to work together with society at large to
tecnología quieren trabajar junto con la sociedad en general a
address the world's most pressing challenges of the world's most urgent
abordar los desafíos mundiales más urgentes
and from there suddenly more easily sally's farmers
y de ahí de repente más fácilmente los agricultores sally 's
it gives us the opportunity to be better prepared to work towards
nos da la oportunidad de estar mejor preparados para trabajar hacia
sustainable society thousand these are from all over europe
sociedad sostenible mil estos es de toda europa
and new friends
y nuevos amigos
you drive socially socially responsible
conduces transformación social responsable
by enhancing the strong alliance of European universities of
al mejorar la alianza fuerte de las universidades europeas de
technology to enable people to develop and use to develop and use science and
tecnología capacitar a las personas para desarrollar y utilizar la ciencia y
technology for the benefit of society and global challenges
la tecnología para beneficio de la sociedad y y retos globales
in opportunities
en oportunidades
making us in improving the European universities of technology alliance
haciendo nosotros en mejorar las universidades europeas de tecnología alliance